{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393727206","data":{"timestamp":" 947393727205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393778835","data":{"timestamp":" 947393778835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393786795","data":{"timestamp":" 947393786794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393798145","data":{"timestamp":" 947393798145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393802871","data":{"timestamp":" 947393802871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393813218","data":{"timestamp":" 947393813217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393823575","data":{"timestamp":" 947393823575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393834644","data":{"timestamp":" 947393834644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393849573","data":{"timestamp":" 947393849573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393862296","data":{"timestamp":" 947393862295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393869162","data":{"timestamp":" 947393869161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393877260","data":{"timestamp":" 947393877260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393889039","data":{"timestamp":" 947393889039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393903386","data":{"timestamp":" 947393903386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393919534","data":{"timestamp":" 947393919534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393934103","data":{"timestamp":" 947393934103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393942085","data":{"timestamp":" 947393942085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393947440","data":{"timestamp":" 947393947440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393955135","data":{"timestamp":" 947393955135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393966415","data":{"timestamp":" 947393966415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393978774","data":{"timestamp":" 947393978774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393986805","data":{"timestamp":" 947393986805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947393997680","data":{"timestamp":" 947393997680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394006818","data":{"timestamp":" 947394006817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394017321","data":{"timestamp":" 947394017321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394029300","data":{"timestamp":" 947394029300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394036291","data":{"timestamp":" 947394036291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394048470","data":{"timestamp":" 947394048470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394061383","data":{"timestamp":" 947394061383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394071195","data":{"timestamp":" 947394071195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394084913","data":{"timestamp":" 947394084913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394092779","data":{"timestamp":" 947394092779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394106421","data":{"timestamp":" 947394106421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394112102","data":{"timestamp":" 947394112101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394124424","data":{"timestamp":" 947394124423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394133142","data":{"timestamp":" 947394133142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394139737","data":{"timestamp":" 947394139737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394157750","data":{"timestamp":" 947394157750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394177306","data":{"timestamp":" 947394177306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394186321","data":{"timestamp":" 947394186321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394190572","data":{"timestamp":" 947394190572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394202040","data":{"timestamp":" 947394202040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394209978","data":{"timestamp":" 947394209978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394221940","data":{"timestamp":" 947394221940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394236320","data":{"timestamp":" 947394236320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394245352","data":{"timestamp":" 947394245352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394249977","data":{"timestamp":" 947394249977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394260189","data":{"timestamp":" 947394260189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394271685","data":{"timestamp":" 947394271685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394285850","data":{"timestamp":" 947394285850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394300350","data":{"timestamp":" 947394300350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394305510","data":{"timestamp":" 947394305510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394313024","data":{"timestamp":" 947394313024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394329273","data":{"timestamp":" 947394329273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394340265","data":{"timestamp":" 947394340265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394352419","data":{"timestamp":" 947394352419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394356662","data":{"timestamp":" 947394356662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394363471","data":{"timestamp":" 947394363471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394373781","data":{"timestamp":" 947394373781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394388830","data":{"timestamp":" 947394388829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394413941","data":{"timestamp":" 947394413941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 1b2440c5-ff64-42ad-9aee-c1981fb5e233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394428550","data":{"timestamp":" 947394428550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 10e5e920-dba4-45d9-b406-8759dbd5c793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394429174","data":{"timestamp":" 947394429173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 10e5e920-dba4-45d9-b406-8759dbd5c793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394429417","data":{"timestamp":" 947394429417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 10e5e920-dba4-45d9-b406-8759dbd5c793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394429616","data":{"timestamp":" 947394429616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 10e5e920-dba4-45d9-b406-8759dbd5c793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947394429712","data":{"timestamp":" 947394429712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_074445"," gameId":" 10e5e920-dba4-45d9-b406-8759dbd5c793"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}